

Roderick Moise

Designer & Developer

W: www.rmoise.com E: roderickfmoise@gmail.com

Github: /rmoise **A:** Berlin, Germany

Linkedin: /roderickmoise

Profile

From the vibrant streets of Brooklyn to Berlin's modern design scene, my career blends a rich background in NYC's ad agencies with a passion for Bauhaus-inspired design. I recently completed a full-stack web development bootcamp at CareerFoundry, where I also built my own website. Driven by a love for coding and design, I strive to create seamless, user-focused experiences that harmonize form and function.

Experience

2023 - 2024

UI / UX Designer

KARL STORZ Berlin, Germany

- Designed landing pages and email templates for KARL STORZ with Figma, enhancing brand and engagement.
- Used Figma to design website components/templates in Opentext CMS and Salesforce. Improved online catalog UX
- Conducted competitor research and user journey mapping, offering insights to inform product development and design decisions for the online catalog.

2019 - 2022

UI / Brand Designer

Kyto Berlin, Germany

- Created a cohesive brand strategy for Kyto, a software as a service company, and new products.
- Created new visual identity, including marketing materials and UI for web and mobile apps, ensuring brand consistency.
- New branding, website, and mobile design boosted customer engagement, leading to Müller Medien acquisition.

2018

Product / Brand Designer

Smunch Berlin, Germany

- Implemented a customer-centric product and brand design strategy for Smunch, a food delivery startup.
- Conducted user research to identify pain points, enhance UX, and update visual identity for promotions.
- Achieved a 156% increase in mobile sessions and up to 2% increase in conversion rates post-launch.

Education

CareerFoundry

Full Stack Dev Certificate Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

Fashion Institute of Technology

BFA in Graphic Design Aug 2013 - May 2015 NY, NY

Skills

Frontend	Backend	Tech Tools	Mobile & Apps	Design & UX
HTML/CSS	Node.js	Git	React Native	Adobe CC
JavaScript	Express	AWS	PWA, Expo	Figma
TypeScript	C#	Firebase		UI/UX Design
Bootstrap	ASP.NET	Heroku		Brand Identity
React	PostgreSQL	Netlify		Prototyping
Angular	MongoDB	Postman		User Research
Tailwind	AWS	Salesforce CRM		Usability

Roderick Moise

Designer & Developer

W: www.rmoise.com
Github: /rmoise

Linkedin: /roderickmoise

E: roderickfmoise@gmail.com

A: Berlin, Germany

.		- 4 -
Pr	ole	ects

2023

Document Management App

Personal Project

- Developed a React and ASP.NET Core document management app with upload, preview, sharing, using PostgreSQL and Azure Blob Storage.
- Added secure authentication and responsive design for all devices
- Deployed on Azure, including user guides for easy adoption.

2023

Meet App

CareerFoundry

- Developed a PWA in React to display events from Google Calendar
- Applied TDD with Jest (unit), Cucumber (acceptance), and Puppeteer (E2E) tests based on user stories.
- Implemented serverless functions using AWS Lambda and used a Kanban board to follow an agile process.

2022

myFlix

CareerFoundry

- Created a non-relational movie database (MongoDB) and built a REST API with Node.JS and Express.
- Tested the API endpoints with Postman, wrote clean and concise documentation, deployed the API with Heroku.
- Designed and developed two single-page, responsive frontend applications using React and Angular.

Language

English: Native

German: Beginner

Haitian Creole: Intermediate